The rules keep changing.
I've been rehearsing every possible outcome.
Once this thought arises, there is no more room for right or wrong.
I am resolved to sever this flood
so that my soul can break free from mediocrity,
from loneliness and distinction.
One more step and you'll fall into madness.
Don't fall down.
I look towards the top.
Chase !
Refined to perfection.
Never retreat, no matter the danger.
I dare to defy the heavens !
Always overcome the obstacles,
ignite the seas with blood,
bloom through trials and tribulations.
Even the sharpest thorns
will be reduced into ashes.
What is there to fear ?
Renegade Immortal\NSubtitles by Bonobosubs\Nhttps://discord.gg/Ceckd4pdVA
Xu Mu ?
I'll remember this name.
Named Xu ?
You also thought of it...
For such a powerful Corporeal Yang cultivator to appear,
it has to be the Xu Family of Planet Dong Lin.
Could this person be...
He is very strong.
Even if he isn't a descendant of Planet Dong Lin,
our Tang Family should avoid provoking him.
But Uncle Ping and the others...
They acted recklessly.
Since they're dead, they're dead.
Understood.
Inside the Celestial Cave
Brother Xu,
this cave seems somewhat peculiar.
Look,
on the walls around us,
there are traces of celestial spiritual energy fluctuations.
It must have been isolated from the outside for very long.
Since this place was left by Celestials,
it's strange that no one visited it
before us.
We have been moving at full speed
for half an hour now.
Why haven't we reached the end yet ?
Just how deep is this tunnel ?
Something's wrong.
Brother Xu,
what is it ?
Do you sense anything unusual ?
What do you mean, Brother Xu ?
Since we entered,
I have been using my Divine Sense to probe the path ahead
and mark our way back.
But I discovered
that the tunnel we are in
is a rune.
Brother Li,
do you recognize this rune ?
This rune is a type of celestial restriction.
It's extremely rare
and can't be used by itself.
It needs to be combined with other runes
to form a restriction formation.
So complex...
Can you tell what kind of formation it is ?
Not yet.
We have too little information
to make a guess.
Before we reach the end,
it will be impossible to determine
what formation it is.
The Celestial Realm has been shattered for so long
but this place still has an active formation ?
Whatever is at the end
is either a great treasure
or a great calamity.
But this is too rare of an opportunity...
Giving up now
would be a waste.
Brother Li,
in that case,
let's go down and see.
But remember, we must act cautiously
and understand the formation
before deciding.
30 minutes later
The end is just ahead !
Brother Xu,
I figured it out.
This formation of runes
has only a single function.
It's for healing.
If I'm not mistaken,
there are 9 such runic tunnels in total.
The 9 runes work together
to create a massive healing formation.
All this time,
it never stopped operating.
Brother Li, do you mean that
all this time,
someone has been healing within
this formation ?
In the Thunder Celestial Realm,
someone who could use so many resources
just for healing
must be...
a Celestial !
The Celestial healing in this formation has already awakened.
He most likely sensed our presence long ago
and allowed us to venture this deep.
It's just a mere restriction.
I'm confident I can open it for you, Brother Xu.
Li Yuan !
What's wrong ?
Brother Xu,
don't you want to learn celestial spells ?
If we can find this Celestial,
we will obtain
countless celestial spells !
Brother Xu, let go of me !
I will open the restriction
Li Yuan isn't this reckless usually.
to get the celestial spells !
Let go of me !
Could it be...?
Li Yuan must have been bewitched
by someone.
What exactly is in there ?
You...
What celestial spell do you wish to learn ?
Have your friend
cast those celestial restrictions
and I will grant all your desires.
Who are you ?
Do you want to learn
or not ?
Countless cultivators chase after celestial spells
and this person offers them so easily ?
There must be something wrong.
No matter how precious the celestial spell,
I will only cultivate the ones
I obtain by myself.
I must never repeat the mistake
of the Celestial Slaughter Art.
I hate cautious people !
This is...
I acted impulsively just now.
I held you back...
It's not your fault.
That power was too strange.
We need to quickly leave this place.
What's this !?
Ji Realm !?
Brother Li,
hurry up !
Brother Xu,
quick !
Wasteland\NThunder Celestial Realm
Brother Xu !
Brother Li,
protect me !
I've never seen Brother Xu look so serious.
What exactly was that crimson light ?
Wang Lin's Sea of Consciousness
The power of this Ji Realm is truly astonishing.
If I hadn't once possessed the Ji Realm myself,
and known how to counter it with origin energy,
then even with my Corporeal Yang's cultivation,
my Origin Soul would have been destroyed by it !
Celestial spells...
Celestial spells !
Not enough !
It's still not enough !
I need more Qi Refiners !
Only 4 seals remain !
Qing Shui...
The day you will die
is approaching !
I finally sealed it...
Who exactly is sealed
behind that vortex ?
To be able to control such a Ji Realm...
Ji Realm cultivators
can't breakthrough above Nascent Soul.
The only exception
was when I met Na Duo.
But that was because his Ji Realm was gifted by a friend,
not cultivated from scratch.
Could it be...
that there is a way
to continue cultivating with the Ji Realm ?
Brother Xu,
how are your injuries ?
I'm fine.
It would be a pity
to just destroy it...
I'd rather sacrifice some origin energy
to keep it.
It may become useful.
Let's go.
We need to find the Collection Pavilion.
a month and a half later
Void\NThunder Celestial Realm
There are too many cultivators suddenly gathering...
Something is wrong.
Their destinations vary...
They're going in all 4 directions.
What happened exactly ?
It's Zhan Konglie !
Apparently,
he has become a Thunder Celestial Messenger.
Zhan Konglie !
with Shengong Hu and Tang Yanfeng, they are the 3 Heroes of the Southern Domain.
All 3 are prodigies of their generation.
They all reached Corporeal Yang at a young age.
They have a lot of potential.
Stop there !
Junior Zhan Konglie,
pays respect to Senior.
Senior !?
But this guy's cultivation is the same as Zhan Konglie's...
Corporeal Yang ?
So he really is a Senior.
I couldn't see him hiding his cultivation before,
and it's the same now.
Where are you going
in such haste ?
Senior,
4 fragments of the Thunder Celestial Realm suddenly gave off
powerful celestial spiritual energy fluctuations.
It's all sealed by restrictions
but we suspect great treasures will appear.
Junior has already agreed with Brother Shengong
to join forces.
Does Senior
have the time
to accompany me ?
I have other matters.
This journey sounds dangerous,
be careful.
Understood !
Junior will remember !
Central fragment\NThunder Celestial Realm
The Collection Pavilion should be right here.
There are indeed restriction fluctuations here
that are similar to celestial restrictions.
Although they are faint,
I can detect something
with my Restriction Heart.
Brother Xu,
I will need some time.
breaking this restriction completely
will likely take months.
With your restrictions
and my speed,
sending me inside
should be feasible.
Good idea !
It's worth a try.
Brother Li,
once I'm inside,
find a place to hide.
After I obtain the celestial spells,
we will leave together.
Restriction Heart, burst !
Colletion Pavilion\NThunder Celestial Realm
Forbidden ground guardian\NYao Family cultivator\NCorporeal Yang
Outsiders of the four great families
who trespass into this forbidden ground
must die !
This is the Thunder Celestial Realm,
the Collection Pavilion is a relic of the past.
Why can the four great families use it freely
but not me ?
Because
you're not qualified.
And Origin Soul that devours thunder !?
Do you intend to keep watching !?
Forbidden ground guardian\NChen Family cultivator\NCorporeal Yang
Forbidden ground guardian\NLu Family cultivator\NCorporeal Yang
Forbidden ground guardian\NSong Family cultivator\NCorporeal Yang
Let me pass,
and we can avoid this fight.
Otherwise, even if I lose,
half of you will die.
Outsider,
you're not qualified to enter !
Then don't blame me for being rude.
Spatial Bending !?
Stop !
What is this !?
I...
want to enter the Collection Pavilion.
I want to enter the Collection Pavilion.
Am I
qualified enough now ?